mortgagefit.com 2019-06-07

# privacy policy - Mortgagefit

## Privacy Policy

At MortgageFit, we take all measures to ensure that your privacy is maintained at each and every phase of our service. Our Privacy Policy highlights the types of information we collect when you use our services, as well as some of the steps we take to secure such information. 

At MortgageFit, ensuring your privacy is our primary concern. We shall not share your personal and private financial details with any third party until and unless you authorize the party. We hope to uphold the faith and trust with which you have entrusted us with your private information to help us process your loan request.

Our Privacy Policy includes certain standards which we maintain and follow while managing information about you and your loan request.

We believe in making you aware of: 

  * Who we are
  * Information which we gather
  * How we use your information
  * Altering your information

Who we are

* * *

MortgageFit is a growing Community of common people, lenders and brokers - an open platform where you can connect to the lender or the broker who matches your requirements. We have a Community of lenders/brokers operating in different states across the globe. Our Community also contributes towards developing this industry by empowering common people with quick mortgage advice and help.

Information which we gather

* * *

The information which we collect prior to matching your requirement includes: 

  * **Information for Loan Request:**  
We require you to provide personal information such as your name, contact number, Social Security Number and email-address. Apart from this, we may ask you to give us your income and financial details depending upon your loan requirement. 
  * **Additional Information for Loan Request:**  
We may also seek supplementary information about you from third party sources. For instance, we may request the credit bureaus for your credit report using your name and Social Security Number. 
  * **Technical information:**  
We often collect and track user information and this ensures that our customers are getting the best of services available. 
  * **Information collected from lenders:**  
We gather information from lenders on their services, their contact number, loan packages, along with point-rate combinations. All such details are given in our Lenders Directory, so that you can search for the lender who matches your requirements. Also, it becomes easier for us to match you with the lender of your choice. 
  * **Information through Calculators:**  
You may use our calculators in order to make financial calculations. We do not collect your personal details while you may input data into the calculators at our site. 

How we use your information 

* * *

We use the information that you provide on your loan request so that we can match you with the lender who can fulfill your needs. We may also send your details to third parties involved in your transaction. 

  * **Sharing information with our Lenders Community:**  
Your information is shared with lenders, banks and mortgage companies at your consent only. We present your credit and loan related details only to those lenders or companies which offer the type of loan program you have opted for. 

Since our lenders will keep and use your information, we recommend you contact them for better information on their own privacy policies, irrespective of whether you qualify for the loan or not.

  * **Distributing Information among third parties:**  
We often distribute information among third parties on behalf of our lenders. We may also notify you in case of any promotional offer from the third party. But without your due consent, we do not reveal your name, address or any identifying information to such parties.

Altering your information

* * *

As our Community member, you can modify and update the details you have already given us. But whichever information is altered, special care is taken as to no such details are misused or lost. Our site is easily navigable and helps you to look out for every information you require for a complete transaction. 

  * **Updating your information:**  
As a Community member, you can always update your personal details through the Control panel. But you need to log in to your account for this purpose. 
  * **Deleting your details:**  
As per the regulations of the Federal and State governments, we cannot delete your information from our databases. Therefore, we store all your details regarding loan request for a considerable period of time. 
  * **Request to stop sending you Emails:**  
We often send private messages to community members in response to their request for our services. But you can always mail us at [mfcare@mortgagefit.com](mailto:mfcare@mortgagefit.com) in case you do not wish to receive further mails. 
  * **Security Policy:**  
We also implement special security measures to protect unauthorized access or alteration, disclosure or destruction of any kind of information.

Our Privacy Policy may change in due course of time. Any relevant change in the policy will be directly communicated through our website at least a week in advance of its implementation. The relevant changes will be secured by the rules and regulations of the old Privacy Policy.

For any additional query, please feel free to contact us any time.
